Joseph Diragi

Website Tech Support Sales

PROFILE

Motivated Software Engineering student seeks remote sales work. I have been in retail sales positions for the past 2 years. I have a lot of experience with customer service, sales, web hosting and server administration. I have built and deployed a few websites using GoDaddy in the past and have worked with wordpress and other more advanced web technologies as well. I'm not sure if it really applies to the role here, but I'm also very well versed in linux sysadmin, so I can help troubleshoot issues with web hosting products if needed.

EXPERIENCE

Retail Sales Consultant, AT&T; Woodstock, GA - 2021-Present

As a retail sales consultant I spent most of my time resolving customer issues and selling products and services to new and existing customers. During my time at AT&T I received many positive customer reviews. I helped bring our store sales up as well as our CSAT (customer review) scores. My experience in this role will help me when interacting with customers, since I spent most of my day interacting with both happy and unhappy customers. It has also provided me with the skillset to teach customers about new technology and provide support if/when they return to the store with questions.

Retail Sales Associate, Atlanta Vapor; Peachtree City, GA = 2020-2021

During my time at Atlanta Vapor I honed my customer service and sales skills. I interacted with customers daily and helped them make decisions on what products would best suit their needs. I helped experienced customers and new customers alike.

Pickup/E-Commerce Associate, Kroger; Peachtree City, GA - 2016-2020

I started my job at Kroger as an E-Commerce Associate. After about a year I assumed the responsibilities of a shift lead. That included making sure each order was picked and ready on time, keeping track of what items were in stock, out of stock, or in different locations such as a display or alternate location. I kept my team updated via walkie when these things changed and kept up morale with various contests and workplace-appropriate walkie banter. Our location was consistently leading our district in terms of items fulfilled and orders on time while I assumed these responsibilities.

Cook, St. Angelo's Pizza; Peachtree City, GA = 2014-2016

I worked at St. Angelo's during high school and my first year of college for some extra spending money. I was responsible for preparing pizzas and other food items when orders were placed. This job helped me to hone my time management skills as well as my customer service skills.

EDUCATION

Kennesaw State University, Kennesaw, GA — BS, Software Engineering

SKILLS

I take pride in my customer service. At every job I've ever had I was consistently commended by management for my customer reviews. I am constantly being mentioned in reviews for outstanding customer service. I am patient and well spoken when interacting with even problem customers.

I am experience in deploying websites to hosting platforms and configuring those platforms to work with domain registries like GoDaddy. My website (jdiggity.me) was configured to work with GitHub pages using CNAME entries. It *is* currently registered with pork bun (sorry) but I've used GoDaddy in the past and will have no trouble at all getting acquainted with the different features and plans GoDaddy has to offer.

4626 Highland Parc Pl SE, Marietta, GA 30067 * (631)576-6115 joyod3@gmail.com